ILGWU Education Department, Jasper Peyton Papers 5780/086
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU Education Department, Jasper Peyton Papers
1952-1982
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Peyton, Jasper
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU)
International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU). Education Dept.
5780/086
16.5 cubic feet
16.5 linear ft.
Correspondence.
The collection contains subject files including correspondence, memorandums, news releases, pamphlets and notices. Some odd photos are dispersed throughout collection. Also included in the collection is Educational Reports to the G.E.B., Educational Activities Reports, questionnaires, and routine paperwork.
5492872
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 04, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 11, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was once one of the largest labor unions in the United States founded in 1900 by local union delegates representing about 2,000 members in cities in the northeastern United States. It was one of the first U.S. Unions to have a membership consisting of mostly females, and it played a key role in the labor history of the 1920s and 1930s. The union is generally referred to as the "ILGWU" or the "ILG". The ILGWU grew in geographical scope, membership size, and political influence to become one of the most powerful forces in American organized labor by mid-century. Representing workers in the women's garment industry, the ILGWU worked to improve working and living conditions of its members through collective bargaining agreements, training programs, health care facilities, cooperative housing, educational opportunities, and other efforts. The ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union in 1995 to form the Union of Needle trades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). UNITE merged with the Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE) in 2004 to create a new union known as UNITE HERE. The two unions that formed UNITE in 1995 represented only 250,000 workers between them, down from the ILGWU's peak membership of 450,000 in 1969.
Biographical / Historical
Jasper Peyton was born in Richmond, Virginia. Peyton studied at the University of the Philippines (Manila), graduated from City College (New York), and was adjunct professor at Fordham University. He attended New York Theological Seminary and was ordained in 1982. From 1950 to 1969, Peyton worked as a pleater and patternmaker, and from 1969 until 1995, he was on staff at the International's Education Department and for a time, serving as the Assistant Education Director. He currently lives in Brooklyn, New York.
Biographical / Historical
Local union's of the ILGWU established and maintained robust, ambitious educational departments early on in the international's history. As these groups grew in size and scope, the international office sought to coordinate and centralize educational programming for the union's members, culminating in the formation of the Educational Department in 1918.
The department's programming included courses at the Workers' University at the Washington Irving High School in New York City, lectures at Unity Centers and Unity Houses in the northeastern United States, and other events. The educational offerings of the International's Education Department were varied, as had been the education departments of the local unions, and included not only classes in labor studies but also courses in languages, music, and the arts. The ILGWU's 1937 musical "Pins and Needles" exemplified the diversity of the union's programs.
Directors of the Education Department, especially Fannia Cohn and Mark Starr, wrote extensively on the ILGWU's programs and worker education in general. Longtime director Gus Tyler not only directed the department, but also served as the ILGWU's on-staff scholar. In later years, the Education Department went beyond collaborating with other education organizations and arranging in-house programs to also supporting post-secondary education for union members and their families.
Scope and Contents
The Education Department records document activities across the entire period of the department's existence, with the bulk of the records covering the 1970s and 1990s. It contains papers from directors of the Education Department: Fannia Cohn, Mark Starr, Gus Tyler, and Kitty Krupat.
The earliest documentation of the department's work is found in the Fannia Cohn papers (5780/049, 5780/049 P); these contain correspondence, subject files, speeches, photographs, and printed material from her work as director of the Educational Department. A microfilm copy of the Fannia Cohn papers held at the New York Public Library (5998 mf) complements the Kheel Center's holdings. Documentation of the work of another longtime leader of the Education Department, Mark Starr, is contained in these records (5780/166, 5780/166 PUBS), as well as in a related collection from Starr on worker education programs (5243).
Documentation of the work of Gus Tyler, who led the merged Education and Political Department after Mark Starr's retirement in 1960, is also contained in the ILGWU records (5780/052, 5780/088, 5780/096). Tyler's papers are complemented by those of Assistant Director Jasper Peyton (5780/086) and Special Projects Coordinator Beverly Shulman (5780/106). These collections contain routine correspondence and memoranda, reports, materials relating to training institutes, seminars, and conferences, and printed material.
The papers of Kitty Krupat, who was serving as Education Director at the time of the ILGWU/ACTWU merger in 1995, constitute the entirety of Education Department records from the 1990s. They include correspondence, memoranda, reports, and financial records relating to the ILGWU's independent and collaborative education projects, including the Worker-Family Education Program, the Joint Union-University Committee on Labor Education, and the Consortium for Worker Education, as well as numerous trainings, conferences, and seminars. Also included in the files are materials from local unions and regional departments of the ILGWU, files on the Internationals' conventions, and reports to the General Executive Board.
In the Jasper Peyton papers, series I contains subject files including correspondence, memoranda, news releases, pamphlets and notices, and routine paperwork. Also included in this series is correspondence materials directly related to Jasper Peyton's duties as Assistant Education Director; most of these materials are from 1971 and 1972. Some odd photos are dispersed through the collection. Series II includes Educational Reports to the General Executive Board, Educational Activities Reports, correspondence, questionnaires, and routine paperwork. Series III includes several issues of Publishers' Weekly and assorted anti-Communist printed material.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780: ILGWU records 5780/106: ILGWU Education Department, Beverly Shulman Papers 5780/138: ILGWU Education Department, Kitty Krupat Papers 5780/166: ILGWU Education Department Records 5780/166 PUBS: ILGWU Education Department Publications 5780/049: ILGWU Education Department, Fannia Cohn Papers 5780/049 P: ILGWU Education Department, Fannia Cohn Photographs 5780/086a mf: ILGWU Education Department, Jasper Peyton Papers Additional on Microfilm
Women's clothing industry--United States.; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- United States.; Clothing trade--United States.; Industrial relations--United States.; Peyton, Jasper.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Educational Dept.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. General Executive Board.
5492872
- Series I: Administrative Files., 1963-1982 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Scope Note: This series contains subject files including correspondence, memorandums, news releases, pamphlets and notices, and routine paperwork. Some odd photos dispersed throughout collection.
- Adult Education, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Affiliate Activities (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Undated. Bicentennial Activities; Classes and Conferences; Trips, Tours, and Outings; Community Affairs; Performing Arts, Theatre, Movies, and Sports.
- AFL-CIO. [folder 1 of 6], 1969-1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Legislative Department Fact Sheets; "Program to Build America's Jobs and Trade in the Seventies"; AFL-CIO Labor Studies Center; correspondence with AFL-CIO Labor Studies Center - Working Americans Bicentennial Projects; re teaching kit; Meany's press release - 11/10/76 Executive Council Meeting; Statement by William E. Pollard, Director AFL-CIO Department of Civil Rights to U.S. Commission on Civil Rights, November 1, 1976; AFL-CIO Film Discussion Guide; correspondence and statement re Multilateral Trade Agreements; Proceedings - Annual AFL-CIO Education Conference 1979; The Full Employment News Reporter; routine.
- AFL-CIO. [folder 2 of 6], 1969-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO. [folder 3 of 6], 1969-1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO. [folder 4 of 6], 1969-1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO. [folder 5 of 6], 1969-1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO. [folder 6 of 6], 1969-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- American Folklife Festival. [folder 1 of 2], 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  "Smithsonian Institute - 1972 Festival of American Life"; financial papers; routine.
- American Folklife Festival. [folder 2 of 2], 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- American Issues Forum, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  "American Society in the Making"; National Bicentennial program
- American Red Cross. First Aid Instructor Training, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Minutes - First Aid project; routine.
- A. Phillip Randolph Institute. [folder 1 of 3], 1974-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  News Releases; 1976 Key List; Educational Fund; routine.
- A. Phillip Randolph Institute. [folder 2 of 3], 1974-1982 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- A. Phillip Randolph Institute. [folder 3 of 3], 1974-1982 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Black Expo '72, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Black Heritage Association, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Urban Task Force; New Directions in Affirmative Action; routine.
- Black Trade Unionists. [folder 1 of 6], 1971-1980 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Black Trade Unionists. [folder 2 of 6], 1971-1980 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Black Trade Unionists. [folder 3 of 6], 1971-1980 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Black Trade Unionists. [folder 4 of 6], 1971-1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Black Trade Unionists. [folder 5 of 6], 1971-1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Black Trade Unionists. [folder 6 of 6], 1971-1980 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  correspondence with Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union; with New York City Central Labor Council AFL-CIO Job Placement Program; Proposals for a Relationship between A. Phillip Randolph Institute and Black Trade Unionists; routine.
- Blood Bank Drive Program. [folder 1 of 4], 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  New York Blood Center; "The Donor"; "Handy Info for Donor Groups"; routine.
- Blood Bank Drive Program. [folder 2 of 4], 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Blood Bank Drive Program. [folder 3 of 4], 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Blood Bank Drive Program. [folder 4 of 4], 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Blood Release Forms. [folder 1 of 2], 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Blood Release Forms. [folder 2 of 2], 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Bowling. [folder 1 of 5], 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Bowling. [folder 2 of 5], 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Bowling. [folder 3 of 5], 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Bowling. [folder 4 of 5], 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Bowling. [folder 5 of 5], 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Bowling. Forms, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Bowling. National ILGWU Bowling Tournament. [folder 1 of 3], 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Bowling. National ILGWU Bowling Tournament. [folder 2 of 3], 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Bowling. National ILGWU Bowling Tournament. [folder 3 of 3], 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation Program (CPR), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Chorus (Chorale). [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1977 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Chorus (Chorale). [folder 2 of 2], 1973-1977 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Chorus, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  Convention, 1977.
- Circus. Ringling Brothers, Barnum, and Bailey Circus, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- College University File, 1972-1981 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  University of Missouri-Columbia; Rutgers University; University of Wisconsin; New York University; Labor Education Center - University of Connecticut; City College of New York; routine.
- Commission on Human Rights, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  News Releases
- Community Relations. [folder 1 of 3], 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  Manhood Foundation, Inc.; Community Church of New York; Council of Churches of City of New York; Center for a Voluntary Society; Regional Plan Association; Seventh Annual New York Consumer Assembly; pamphlets; routine.
- Community Relations. [folder 2 of 3], 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Community Relations. [folder 3 of 3], 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Community Service Committee. Performing Arts, 1971-1977 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Congressional District Committee, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Correspondence. General, 1976-1982 (Box 3, Folder 7-14)
- Correspondence. Affiliates. [folder 1 of 3], 1971-1976 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Correspondence. Affiliates. [folder 2 of 3], 1971-1976 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Correspondence. Affiliates. [folder 3 of 3], 1971-1976 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Correspondence. Education Directors/Managers, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Correspondence. Inter-Office Memorandums. [folder 1 of 4], 1972-1979 (Box 3, Folder 18a)
- Correspondence. Inter-Office Memorandums. [folder 2 of 4], 1972-1979 (Box 3, Folder 18b)
- Correspondence. Inter-Office Memorandums. [folder 3 of 4], 1972-1979 (Box 3, Folder 18c)
- Correspondence. Inter-Office Memorandums. [folder 4 of 4], 1972-1979 (Box 3, Folder 18d)
- Correspondence. Financial, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Directory Listing Changes, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Education Directors/Managers. General. [folder 1 of 4], 1972-1979 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  General Mailings and Material Sent; "Wages, Prices, and Profits" by Leon H. Keyserling; routine.
- Education Directors/Managers. General. [folder 2 of 4], 1972-1979 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Education Directors/Managers. General. [folder 3 of 4], 1972-1979 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Education Directors/Managers. General. [folder 4 of 4], 1972-1979 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Education Directors/Managers. Meetings. [folder 1 of 7], 1972-1980 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  Lists; Attendance sheets; correspondence; routine.
- Education Directors/Managers. Meetings. [folder 2 of 7], 1972-1980 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Education Directors/Managers. Meetings. [folder 3 of 7], 1972-1980 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Education Directors/Managers. Meetings. [folder 4 of 7], 1972-1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Education Directors/Managers. Meetings. [folder 5 of 7], 1972-1980 (Box 4, Folder 1a)
- Education Directors/Managers. Meetings. [folder 6 of 7], 1972-1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Education Directors/Managers. Meetings. [folder 7 of 7], 1972-1980 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Education Report Convention, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Surveys; histories; statements; political and educational reports; routine.
- Exhibit, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Fashion Festival, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  newspaper clippings; routine.
- Fashion Institute of Technology, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Productivity Report (FIT); "Partnership For Progress" -Urban Affairs at FIT; Urban Affairs Award Banquet; routine.
- Finance, 1972-1979 (Box 4, Folder 8-20)
  Checks; receipts; invoices; routine.
- Finance. Insurance, bills, etc. [folder 1 of 2], 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  Checks; receipts; routine.
- Finance. Insurance, bills, etc. [folder 2 of 2], 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Finance. Jasper Peyton, 1972-1978 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- First-Aid, 1975-1979 (Box 5, Folder 1-12)
  correspondence; session worksheets; Photos; routine.
- Food Stamp Program. [folder 1 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  correspondence; checks; receipts; purchase order receipts; "Myths About the Food Stamp Program"; "Nutrition: A Neglected Goal"; routine.
- Food Stamp Program. [folder 2 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Foreign Visitors, 1972-1979 (Box 5, Folder 15-23)
  correspondence with African-American Institute; Asian-American Free Labor Institute; Nagoya Regional Team; American Institute for Free Labor Development; Governmental Affairs Institute; Visitor Program Service; Observation Team on Worker's Education to Canada and America; Foreign Press Center; "The American Worker and His Union"; routine.
- Freedom Leadership Foundation (Box 5, Folder 24)
  Undated.
- Grand Music Hall of Israel, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- High School Equivalency, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- High School of Fashion Industries, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- History, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Legislative Acts; Firsts Events; ILGWU Events; routine
- Imports. [folder 1 of 6], 1971-1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Newspaper clippings; ILGWU National Legislative Conference - Action on Imports
- Imports. [folder 2 of 6], 1971-1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Imports. [folder 3 of 6], 1971-1976 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Imports. [folder 4 of 6], 1971-1976 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Imports. [folder 5 of 6], 1971-1976 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations. Twentieth Century Trade Union Women, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Insurance, 1964-1971 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Imports. [folder 6 of 6], 1971-1976 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Justice, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Labor Theatre File. [folder 1 of 3], 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  The Now Drug Scene; routine.
- Labor Theatre File. [folder 2 of 3], 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Labor Theatre File. [folder 3 of 3], 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- La Voz Latina, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Minutes. General (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Mural. 75th Anniversary, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- National Alliance For Safer Cities. see Safer Cities (Box 6, Folder 17a)
- National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP). [folder 1 of 4], 1975-1979 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP). [folder 2 of 4], 1975-1979 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP). [folder 3 of 4], 1975-1979 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP). [folder 4 of 4], 1975-1979 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- National Congress of Neighborhood Women, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- National Council of Negro Women. (Box 6, Folder 22a)
- National Manpower Institute, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  Invitational Conference on continuing Education, Manpower Policy and Lifelong Learning National Advisory Panel; routine.
- Newspaper Clippings. [folder 1 of 2], 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Newspaper Clippings. [folder 2 of 2], 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- New York Central Labor Council, 1971-1977 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- New York State File. [folder 1 of 4], 1972-1975 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  Spanish High School Equivalency Guidelines (NYS); Budget Summary; Profile of People, Jobs, and Housing; Business Trends in New York State; Business Statistics of New York State; routine.
- New York State File. [folder 2 of 4], 1971-1977 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- New York State File. [folder 3 of 4], 1971-1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- New York State File. [folder 4 of 4], 1971-1977 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Parliament Procedure Class, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  "The ABC of Parliamentary Law"; routine.
- Pins and Needles Production, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Political Department. [folder 1 of 3], 1972-1975 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  Legislative newsletter; Minimum Wage Legislation; routine.
- Political Department. [folder 2 of 3], 1972-1975 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Political Department. [folder 3 of 3], 1972-1975 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Political. Education Directors' Conference. [folder 1 of 2], 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Political. Education Directors' Conference. [folder 2 of 2], 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Price Watch, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  General Information - Economic Stabilization Program; Price Watch Activities; routine.
- Research Department, 1968-1974 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Learner Regulations in the Apparel Industries; routine.
- Safer Cities File (National Alliance For Safer Cities). [folder 1 of 6], 1972-1978 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Minutes; brochures; newsletters; "Laws, Licenses and the Offender's Right To Work"; "The Employment Problems of Ex-Offenders"; routine.
- Safer Cities File (National Alliance For Safer Cities). [folder 2 of 6], 1972-1978 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Safer Cities File (National Alliance For Safer Cities). [folder 3 of 6], 1972-1978 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Safer Cities File (National Alliance For Safer Cities). [folder 4 of 6], 1972-1978 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Safer Cities File (National Alliance For Safer Cities). [folder 5 of 6], 1972-1978 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Safer Cities File (National Alliance For Safer Cities). [folder 6 of 6], 1972-1978 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- S.T.E.P.. Scholarship Training Education Political. [folders 1-8 of 17], 1971-1974 (Box 7, Folder 19-26)
- S.T.E.P.. Scholarship Training Education Political. [folders 9-17 of 17], 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 1-9)
  Newsletters; general news releases; reports and information; correspondence; S.T.E.P. - pre-public proofs; Photos; routine.
- School for Organizers. [folder 1 of 3], 1976 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Attendance and participants lists; correspondence; "Conditions In The Women's Garment Industry"; routine.
- School for Organizers. [folder 2 of 3], 1976 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- School for Organizers. [folder 3 of 3], 1976 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- School for Organizers. Essays, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  Applicant Essays
- School for Organizers. Finance, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  Payroll Change Notices; check copies; routine.
- School for Organizers. Resumes. [folder 1 of 2], 1976 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- School for Organizers. Resumes. [folder 2 of 2], 1976 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Spanish Class. [folder 1 of 2], 1970-1981 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  Class attendance lists; correspondence; routine.
- Spanish Class. [folder 2 of 2], 1970-1981 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Tours. [folders 1-3 of 10], 1971-1976 (Box 8, Folder 19-21)
- Tours. [folders 4-10 of 10], 1971-1976 (Box 9, Folder 1-7)
  Tour Information; routine.
- Training Institute. General, 1963-1975 (Box 9, Folder 8-16)
  Attendance lists; programs and class schedules; correspondence; candidate applications; correspondence with Saul Nesselroth; organizing information; photos; routine.
- Training Institute. Advanced Staff, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Training Institute. Central States region Institute, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Training Institute. Instructors. [folder 1 of 2], 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Training Institute. Instructors. [folder 2 of 2], 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Training Institute. Rutgers: Labor Program Institute of Management and Labor Relations, 1964-1966 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  Sponsored by South Jersey-Philadelphia Joint Board
- Training Institute. Summer ILGWU Training Institute. [folder 1 of 2], 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Training Institute. Summer ILGWU Training Institute. [folder 2 of 2], 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Training Institute. Upper South Institute, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- United Italian American Labor Council, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Four Freedoms Award to Louis Stulberg
- Unity House, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Vermont Weekend, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 3)